# Ivan Telles, Software Developer

Norwalk, United States, 714-476-4523, tellezivan7@gmail.com

PROFILE

Experienced software developer with over 5 years building responsive web and mobile applications using modern frameworks and libraries like React/React Native. Currently working under a SaaS based Fin-tech company building mobile and online banking solutions for Credit Unions, while gaining hands-on experience with .NET Framework, ASP.NET, C#, and Entity Framework to develop REST APIs.

#### EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Aug 2022 — Present

## Software Developer, Mahalo Technologies, Inc

- Accomplished creating a multi-language translation system supporting English and Spanish across
  customer-facing site content, increasing user accessibly support by 50%, by developing a custom JSON
  translation API pipeline accessible to 10+ non-technical credit union admins through a custom admin
  portal dashboard.
- Developed an accurate mobile check deposit solution for our fintech IOS/Android mobile banking app supporting 8 remote deposit vendors, measured by an increase of 30% in daily mobile deposits, by building a custom mobile integration that communicated with native specific mobile support via NativeBridge.
- Implemented scalable multiplatform MFA solution across 10+ live production banking apps, resulting in 50% reduction of identity and financial fraud threats for over 500k customer account holders.
- Cultivated a cross-platform bill pay service across web and native mobile apps to add/manage payees
  and enable one-time/recurring payments, measured by a 20% rise in bill pay digital engagement within 3
  months post-launch, by creating reusable React components interfacing with .NET APIs.
- Configured a multistep a skip payment solution on web and native iOS/Android apps supporting 20+ distinct credit union parameter rules, measured by streamlined servicing of 500K+ members requests over 10+ successful credit union implementations, via React forms allowing support for customization of member eligibility and user journeys by individual credit union admins.

Oct 2021 — Jul 2022

# Front-End Developer, PlayerBoost

Remote

- Utilized Firestore Database to compile user's orders, payment information, payouts, and profile preferences.
- Worked closely with a Senior React Developer to create a strong, effectively responsive dashboard for users to manage, communicate, and share their gaming experience.
- Used Redux for state management, and dispatched user controlled actions to render responsive UI components.

EDUCATION

Aug 2017 — Dec 2019

### Bachelor of Science in Marketing, CSUDH

SKILLS MongoDB TypeScript
Bootstrap React

Node.js Mobile Development

HTML & CSS React Native

SQL Azure DevOps

Git C# .NET Core

JavaScript Entity Framework

COURSES

Jul 2023 — Aug 2023 C# .NET Core 7 with MS SQL

Aug 2023 — Sep 2023 Ultimate ASP.NET Core Web API Development Guide

Oct 2023 — Nov 2023 Complete C# Programming Course